infineon.com 2017-09-18

# Privacy Policy - Infineon Technologies

Protection of our user’s privacy is very important to Infineon. Infineon always complies with the applicable laws on privacy and data security. The following sections explain what type of information Infineon may collect and how Infineon handles it during your use of our website.

  1. **Scope of this Privacy and Cookie Policy**  
This privacy and cookie policy applies to all data which is collected and used www.infineon.com by the Infineon group of companies (hereinafter "Infineon"). By using our website you consent to the collection and usage of your data and information in accordance with this privacy and cookie policy as well as the terms of use. They do not apply to other online or offline Infineon websites, products, services or apps. This website is hosted by our external agency partner Virtual Identity AG, Munich, Germany.
  2. **Collection of Site Usage Data**  
By visiting our website, our web servers automatically store the IP address and the domain from which access to the website is made, the date and time of your visit, the website of ours that you visit, as well as technical information about the visit (e.g. http method, http version, http status code, and browser used). 
    1. Infineon collects no further personal data (e.g. names, addresses, phone numbers, or e-Mail addresses) on our website, unless you have provided us with such data voluntarily (e.g. through registration, participation in a survey, a contest, or in the execution of a contract). If you login as a user on our website, the user ID required for the login is also stored.
    2. In some of our web applications we are creating a unique Infineon web profile for you to store your personal settings, e.g. simulation configurations, shopping cart, favorites etc. This data might be used for statistical purposes, personalizing your online experience as well as for market analyses.
  3. **Purpose**  
Infineon collects user data as describes below in order to make communication with you more personal and interactive. With your data, you are helping us to make our customer service more efficient and continuously improve our website. When you provide us with personal data, Infineon uses it primarily to respond to your inquiries, to process your orders, to provide specially-tailored information or services, and to strengthen our customer relationship. 
  4. **myInfineon**  
myInfineon is the “web single sign on” for Infineon services though you have just one email address and password to remember. myInfineon has built-in rules and functions which determine the services and content each user may access and use. When services require higher security (e.g. a one-time password to access confidential data), the user does not have to login again, but needs additional credentials (second factor authentication) which will be send via SMS*.

How can users access to myInfineon?

Users have to register once to create a myInfineon account. Some personal data is collected during registration for “myInfineon”. Infineon will ask you for your first name, last name, e-mail address, your country, and your company’s name. Once you have registered, you are no longer anonymous to Infineon. After registration, you can use the registered online services.

myInfineon is available from the myInfineon login menu on every www.infineon.com page. Users must login to reach myInfineon customer portal with profile and interest sections or to consume content protected by myInfineon login (like “Insight Sales” content, online simulations, downloads etc.). There is also the option to “stay logged in”.

    1. **my Profile**  
Your login data and your personal data are accessible to you only if you have logged in with your username and password. You may check, change, or delete the personal data you have entered to your myInfineon profile and change your password any time.  
After your registration you can add further information like your profession, industry you are working in, mobile phone number and business phone number. You can also add information about your design projects you are working on to receive support from Infineon. This information is not mandatory to use myInfineon and can be skipped. This information and your profile, are both protected by your password, which means only you can access this personal information. Infineon recommends not share your password with anyone. Whenever Infineon works with your personal data, it will be treated confidentially and in accordance with this privacy policy. Infineon strives to protect your personal data through the application of high security standards.
    2. **my Interests**  
In addition to data entered in your profile section, Infineon may ask you about your product and application interests or preferences in order to provide you tailored information and improve your experience of our website.   
Within myInfineon in the my Interest section you can select the following: 
      * Applications of interest
      * Products of interest
    3. **my Subscriptions**  
Within my Subscriptions you can manage your data for the reception of information regarding our company, products, events or online trainings through one of our applications (e.g. via e-Mail), you may withdraw your consent at any time with effect for the future (as described below).
    4. **my Help  
** Under the section my Help you can find the following: Support Chat, Support Form, Support FAQs, the Technical Assistance Center and our Toll Free Call Center. 

**Support Chat  
** Data collected during the use of the chat system, as well as the content of chats, will be used for the proper processing of your requests.  
You also have the option to use the chat function anonymously without giving your name.  
After Infineon responds to your request, the content of the chat will be processed for the purposes of quality assurance, and to improve our services. 

**Support Form  
** When filling out one of our support forms, your contact data will be passed along in order to get back to you to solve your queries.

  5. **Disclosure  
** Communication and Advertisement: Occasionally Infineon uses and shares your information within the Infineon Group (e.g. marketing department) in order to get a better understanding of you and your business needs, as well as to improve our products and services. 

Partners and Distributors: Infineon (or a third party on our behalf) may use personal data to get in contact with you regarding an offer or survey. Infineon may also pass on personal information to our network of certified distribution partners, if this facilitates a completion of a transaction with you (e.g. if Infineon needs to send you products). Your data might be shared with further third parties if this serves your business interests. For example, if Infineon sends products to you, Infineon transmits personal data to suppliers, distributors, or third parties that work with us. 

Authorities: Data shall only be sent to government bodies and authorities in accordance with mandatory national legal provisions. In all other cases, Infineon will not pass your data on to third parties without your express consent. Our employees are sworn to secrecy and to protect all personal data.

  6. **Right of Objection  
** You can object the collection and use of this data for the future and unsubscribe from any Infineon communication to which you have subscribed. Every e-Mail from Infineon contains a link to your "my profile,” where you can view, change, or delete the data you’ve shared with us, and also subscribe or unsubscribe to/from information services.
  7. **Personalization (Cookies, Web Beacons)  
** Infineon uses cookies, web beacons, and the personal data that you provide us to personalize the online presentation for you and to improve our services. Infineon uses cookies, for example, to recall the country and language preferences you have selected on our website. Web beacons from third-party service providers are used to help deliver cookies and gather usage and performance data. 

You have a variety of tools to control cookies, web beacons and similar technologies, including browser controls to block and delete cookies and controls from some third-party analytics service providers to opt out of data collection through web beacons (as described below). 

A cookie is a text file that is stored on your computer which makes it possible to analyze your use of the website. Cookies are sent from the Infineon web server to help your browser to identify you and to enable Infineon to provide you with customized and personalized services. All web pages by Infineon which ask you to log in, or which are customized, require cookies. If you do not want us to recognize your computer (hard disk cookies), you can also delete cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or warn you before a cookie is stored by adjusting your browser settings. Your browser and other choices may impact your experiences with our features.

    1. **Adobe Analytics  
** Infineon stores anonymized user information on this website using the Adobe Analytics tool. This involves using cookies from a third party. These are used for the purpose of optimizing the website and are not connected with personal data without the explicit consent of the user. You can, however, object to this data collection and opt out with effect for the future. The web analytics services also use cookies that are stored on your computer and make it possible to analyze your use of the website. The information generated by a cookie of your use of this website is transmitted exclusively in an anonymous form to a server operated by the web analysis service, and is then stored there.

 **Opt out:  
** You can block the collection or processing of data generated by the cookie related to your visit to our website by Adobe, by stating your intention to opt-out via the following link:  
<http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html>

    2. **Eloqua  
** Oracle’s Eloqua server is located in Amsterdam. Eloqua places a permanent cookie on the respective on our website, unless an Eloqua cookie is already present on your device. Infineon may use the Eloqua cookie to analyze your use of our websites so that Infineon can continuously personalize our communication to you. E-Mails sent by Eloqua include tracking technologies. Infineon uses this information primarily to find out what topics you’re interested in by monitoring which e-Mails are opened and which links are clicked on. This information will help us to improve the e-Mails Infineon sends to you and the services Infineon provides. 

**Opt out:**  
If you wish to block the use of Eloqua cookies on your device for the future, you can do so via this link: <http://www.oracle.com/us/legal/privacy/privacy-policy/index.html#opt-out>[ ](http://www.oracle.com/us/legal/privacy/privacy-policy/index.html#opt-out)

    3. **Google Analytics**  
Our website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies. Information gained by cookies about your use of this website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to a Google server in the U.S. and stored there. Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, compile reports on website activity for website operators, and provide other website-use and Internet-related services. Google may also transmit this information to third parties where required by law, or in cases where third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may block the installation of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser; however Infineon points out that if you do, you may not be able to use all the features of this website. By using this site, you agree to the processing of data collected about you by Google in the manner described above and for the aforementioned purpose.

 **Opt out:  
**[https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de   
](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de)[  
](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de)For more information on Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy, please visit <http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/de.html> or <https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/>[  
](https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/)

  8. **Links to Other Websites  
** Our website may contain links to websites of other providers to which this Privacy Policy does not extend. If the usage of web pages of other providers is connected with the collection, processing, or use of personal data, please see the respective privacy policies of those providers.  
Infineon assumes no responsibility for the content of these websites.
  9. **Twitter, Facebook, YouTube & Co.  
**The social media links embedded on our website (Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, Google+, WeChat, LinkedIn etc.) are not integrated through a "Social Plugin". When you visit our website, no direct connection to social media servers is created. Clicking on the respective social media button creates a connection the respective social media service.
  10. **Children’s Information  
** Infineon does not seek information from persons less than 13 years of age, and no information should be submitted to this website by visitors less than 13 years of age.
  11. **Security  
** Infineon has taken extensive technical and operational safeguards to protect your data against accidental or intentional manipulation, loss, destruction, or unauthorized access. Our security procedures are regularly reviewed and adapted in line with technological advancements.
  12. **Retrieval of Privacy Policy  
** You can retrieve information about the Infineon Privacy Policy at any page on the Infineon website via a hyperlink in the footer.  
At the end of this page you will find the date of the most recent changes to the Privacy Policy.
  13. **Note  
** In order to keep up with the continuous development of the Internet, Infineon may amend this Privacy Policy at any time in compliance with data protection regulations.
  14. **Contact to Data Protection Officer    
**You can contact us at any time regarding privacy rights concerns at the following e-Mail address: dataprotection@infineon.com, or send a letter to the mailing address given below. 

Please provide us with your contact details, the name of the Infineon website or service in question, and a detailed description of your request or your privacy/data protection issue.

To the Data Protection Officer  
Infineon Technologies AG  
IFAG BC-DPC  
81726 Munich  
Germany

*Those services will be provided [ZEITRAHMEN]
